Hello hello everyone how are you all I am
your personal advisor Amit Raj Sharma and
you are watching this real video I
want to give you a piece of information right at the beginning of the video,
you all must be knowing that
Bharti AXA General Insurance Company
Limited is a take over of ICICI Lambda.
In today's video we are discussing
with you the Smart Super Health Insurance Plan.
This plan is available
in both individual and family floater categories. The
plan which is a point system
option, 2 year and 3 year
option is available in this plan.
Talking about the sum insured option, the minimum is
Rs 5 lakh and the maximum is Rs 1 crore.
You are getting the option of free
hospitalization for seven days. Post
hospitalization you are getting 90 days
performance is 1.81.
Talking about the entries element, if you do
this policy of account as an individual then from 5 years
to 65 years as an ambassador, let me
tell you something about it. Family  If it happens, then it
depends on the sandalwood, from the 10th
day onwards, so the age of this year is here, the
term regarding the pre-medical test,
if the entry is 45 years old or capable and up to
Rs 10 lakh is being taken, then there is
no requirement of pre-medical test,
right, but if the entry is 46 years old or if the entry is being taken
more than Rs 10 lakh, then there will be
pre-medical test, only after that
you will be able to apply here, but
half of which will be borne by the ghost and the company, the
expenses from organ donor, you will get full support for that
under the news, see
t-20, half a spoon of dry ginger, you will get to see the interview,
which is 130,
you are also getting undercover Ayush treatment,
which you call Domeshwari hospitalization, which is
also called treatment, you are also getting half a
spoon of Ashwagandha news, restoration,
this point to recharge, you
get 200% airfare support,
but when the basic expenses are over, then
it becomes active, road
ambulance expenses  If we talk then
you get ₹3000 per hospitalization.
Now comes the matter of Conviction Benefit. Now
you know that the benefit which is given if you are
admitted in the hospital for a long time like at least 10 days, then
you get a tax
benefit there. If Chamak
water is between ₹10 lakh to ₹20 lakh and
Raja is between ₹20 lakh to ₹3000. If you
understand that you are a graduate then you must have given a spoon of dry ginger worth ₹15 and ₹50 lakh to
only one crore rupees, then
you get ₹20000 as
balance benefit. There is
emergency treatment on Twitter. Now I am telling
you that only in accidental cases, if there is an
accidental case, then within a year there
is a limit of 30 days. If
this is your understanding, it is between ₹10 lakh to ₹20 lakh
or in between and ₹1000 and ₹20 lakh, no matter how much it
stops  rs.10000 okay sir
so there is a limit of 30 days in this and
I have already told you this thing here old
now when it comes to animal sitting where
you need vaccination recipe
monkeytalk etc bites the house then in such a situation
if the spoon is from 10 lakh to 20 lakh
then if your support is from 20 lakh to
1 crore then you get ₹5000,
news of this gets within this
if someone has a dental emergency only vaccine tent
but if dental treatment is
needed YouTube accident
and the understanding is from 20 lakh to 30 lakh
then you will get ₹5000 here and the dedication
increases from 50 lakh to one side means ₹1 means
you will get ₹2000
for an air ambulance also you get to watch some obscene news
means you get the news
if your sum insured is from 20 lakh
to 30 lakh then  1 lakh rupees if it is from 50 lakh to
1 crore then up to this
entire process means the limit up to 2 lakh rupees will be
here, you are getting
benefit in it and there is no claim bonus, now
see here if the entry limit is
less than 45 years then you will get 50% and up
to 100% you will get 100% after two years,
if the internship is more than 45,000
and up to 65 years you will get 20%, so keep getting
100%,
subscribe to the
channel, you will get it
[Music] If you are
admitted in a hospital then there are these Jhalars,
Pride Awards, trees etc. all the
countries are up, so one way of doing that is suppose
if your news is between 5 lakh to
all the elements then there is an
option of ₹500 or 1000 per day, if your tomato
takes back 10 lakh then there is an option of ₹500, 1000 or 2000
per day, you will use any one of these
20 lakh  If there is a
spoon of one rupee above this, then you will be able to choose any one as per the option of ₹500 and ₹1000 ₹2000 ₹3000
and this will be possible
only for a point senior maximum 30 days,
you have to keep this thing in mind, now the
third thing that you don't have is regarding maternity cover
or intelligence maternity benefit, for this, by
taking the thing in the 45 year exam, the
government has made ads so that it can make
a move for women, then in the coming time, this
health insurance policy will also be great,
I am telling you this thing, it will be
available, if your policy term is of 1
year, then from today,
with the shine of seven and a half times, you get Rs 35000 madam 2099,
this ribbon center news will
come and if it is 10 to 20 lakhs then Rs 50 thousand
if Dashrath, this means by bringing tomato paste from 20 lakhs to 30, then Rs
75 thousand and if from fifty
lakhs to one  If you have paid ₹10,
you will get ₹1 lakh.
Newborn baby one bloody told you that you will
get it from Deoband for constipation and if you put onion then there will be a
waiting period of 9 inches and delivery is
required undercover along with diet and fitness body system is
double let's talk about cigarettes in a few
seconds along with
seven days waiting period along with that there is travels fee of this day but I don't you get testing genetic disorder in tronica serious problems this [music] there is specific disease in which knee replacement oh wow there is meeting for hospitalization you get a waiting
period of 30 days
you all know this product 15 days
Congress practice Zinta on
policy renewal you
also get a free health check-up if you want
positive news speaker only
like the video and tell others understand anything
that insurance is an introduction and
protection is never incomplete
thank you very much
[music]